export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'I didn‘t know what to do, but then an idea suddenly ____ to me.',
    translate: '我不知道该做什么，但突然间我有了一个主意。',
    options: ['A．appeared', 'B．happened', 'C．occurred', 'D．emerged'],
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'A pair of spectacles ____ what I need at the moment.',
    translate: '此刻我需要的是一副眼镜。',
    options: ['A．is', 'B．are', 'C．has', 'D．hav'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'You had better ____ a doctor as soon as possible.',
    translate: '你最好尽快去看医生。',
    options: ['A．seeing', 'B．saw', 'C．see', 'D．seen'],
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '____ these honors he received a sum of money.',
    translate: '除了这些荣誉外，他还得到了一笔钱。',
    options: ['A．Except', 'B．But', 'C．Besides', 'D．Outside'],
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Would you let ____ to the park with my classmate, Mum?',
    translate: '妈，让我和同学一起去公园好吗？',
    options: ['A．me go', 'B．me going', 'C．I go', 'D．I going'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Neither Bill nor his parents ____ at home.',
    translate: '比尔和他的父母都不在家。',
    options: ['A．is', 'B．has', 'C．are', 'D．was'],
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'If you don’t want to get wet, you had better ____ this umbrella with you.',
    translate: '如果你不想被弄湿，最好带上这把伞。',
    options: ['A．take', 'B．to take', 'C．taken', 'D．for taking'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Measles _____ a long time to get over.',
    translate: '麻疹需要很长一段时间才会治好。',
    options: ['A．spend', 'B．spends', 'C．take', 'D．takes'],
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '-Do you want to wait? -Five days ____ too long for me to wait.',
    translate: '您愿意等吗？ 五天等待的时间对于我来说太长了。',
    options: ['A．was', 'B．were', 'C．is', 'D．are'],
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'There ____ a book and some magazines on the desk.',
    translate: '桌子上有一本书和一些杂志。',
    options: ['A．is', 'B．are', 'C．have', 'D．has'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: '-It‘s a good idea. But who’s going to ____ the plan? -I think John and Peter will.',
    translate: '这是个好主意。但谁去执行计划呢？我认为约翰和比德可以去执行这个计划。',
    options: ['A．carry out', 'B．get through', 'C．take in', 'D．set aside'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'The computer system ____ suddenly while he was searching for information on the Internet.',
    translate: '在他上网查找资料的时候计算机系统突然瘫痪了。',
    options: ['A．broke down', 'B．broke out', 'C．broke up', 'D．broke in'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'If she wants to stay thin, she must make a ___ in her diet.',
    translate: '如果她想保持身材苗条，就必须在饮食上有所改变。',
    options: ['A．change', 'B．turn', 'C．run', 'D．Go'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: '____ the War of Independence, the United States was an English colony.',
    translate: '在独立战争以前，美国是英国的一个殖民地。',
    options: ['A．Before', 'B．At', 'C．In', 'D．Between'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'A police officer claimed that he had attempted to ____ paying his fare.',
    translate: '警官说这个年轻人试图拒付费用。',
    options: ['A．avoid', 'B．reject', 'C．refuse', 'D．neglect'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'I tried to put ____ a telephone call to him, but his line was always busy.',
    translate: '我想打电话给他，但总是占线。',
    options: ['A．Over', 'B．into', 'C．away', 'D．through'],
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'I hadn‘t seen him for years, but I ____ his voice on the telephone.',
    translate: '我多年没见他，但在电话里听出了他的声音。',
    options: ['A．realized', 'B．recognized', 'C．discovered', 'D．heard'],
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'She wonders ____ will happen to her private life in the future.',
    translate: '她不知道未来在她私人生活中会发生什么事。',
    options: ['A．that', 'B．it', 'C．this', 'D．what'],
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'The higher the temperature, ____ the liquid evaporates.',
    translate: '温度越高，液体蒸发得越快。',
    options: ['A．the faster', 'B．the more fast', 'C．the slower', 'D．the more slower'],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'Australia is one of the few countries ____ people drive on the left of the road.',
    translate: '澳大利亚是少数几个沿左侧开车的国家之一。',
    options: ['A．which', 'B．that', 'C．where', 'D．on which'],
    answer: 'C',
  },
];
